creditonebank.com 2016-08-18

# Privacy Policy

     Privacy Policy
            &
Online Privacy Statement

M-117638                                                                                                                                Rev 07/2016
  FACTS                WHAT DOES CREDIT ONE BANK, N.A. DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
   Why?         Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some
                but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.
                Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
   What?        The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This
                information can include:
                • Social Security number and income
                • credit history and credit score
                • payment history and transaction history
   How?         All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the
                section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the
                reasons Credit One Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                                                   Does Credit One              Can you limit this
                    Reasons we can share your personal information                                Bank, N.A. share?                  sharing?
 For our everyday business purposes—
 such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court                          YES                          NO
 orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes—
 to offer our products and services to you                                                                 YES                          NO
 For joint marketing with other ﬁnancial companies                                                         YES                          NO
 For our afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes—
 information about your transactions and experiences                                                       YES                          NO
 For our afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes—
 information about your creditworthiness                                                                   YES                         YES
 For our afﬁliates to market to you                                                                        YES                         YES
 For our nonafﬁliates to market to you                                                                     YES                         YES
   To limit            • Call 800-796-6245
   our sharing         Please  Note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this
                       notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
                       However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
   Questions?          Call 877-825-3242
  What we do
   How does Credit One              To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures
   Bank protect my                  that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards, secured files and secured
   personal information?            buildings.
   How does Credit One              We collect your personal information, for example, when you
   Bank collect my                  • apply for a loan or give us your contact information
   personal information?            • pay your bill or use your credit card
   ?                                • give us your income information
                                    We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
   Why can’t I limit sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                    • sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
                                    • affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                    • sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                    State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for
                                    your rights under state law.
   What happens when I limit        Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
   sharing for an account I
   hold jointly with someone
   else?

   Page 2
   Definitions
   Affiliates                         Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                      • Our Affiliates include the Sherman Financial Group LLC family of companies, including Resurgent
                                         Capital Services, LP.
   Nonaffiliates ?                    Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non financial companies.
                                      • Nonaffiliates we share with can include retail lenders, insurance companies, direct marketing companies,
                                         loan lead providers, customer service agencies and collection agencies.
   Joint Marketing                    A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or
                                      services to you.
                                      • Our joint marketing partners include credit card companies, financial institutions and loan service
                                         providers.
   Other important information
 Vermont Residents - Except as permitted by law, we will not share information we collect about you with nonaffiliated or affiliated
 partners.
 California Residents - Except as permitted by law, we will not share information we collect about you with nonaffiliated or joint
 marketing partners while you are a resident of California.
 Nevada Residents - You may call 1-800-796-6245 to be placed on our Do Not Call List. For more information, visit
 www.CreditOneBank.com or mail your request to Credit One Bank, P.O. Box 98871, Las Vegas, NV 89193-8871. You may also
 contact the Bureau of Consumer Protection by phone at 702-486-3132, by email at aginfo@ag.nv.gov, or by mail at Bureau of
 Consumer Protection, Office of the NevadaAttorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101.
C50-00440 05/16
© 2016 Credit One Bank, N.A. All rights reserved.
  Credit One®, Credit One Bank® and corresponding logos are federally registered trademarks.

                                                                                          Rev 07/2016
Online Privacy Statement
This Online Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement") describes Credit One Bank's online and
mobile privacy practices and applies to websites, online applications that run on smartphones,
tablets, mobile devices ("apps"), and other online services that we offer which link to this Privacy
Statement.
Information you provided Credit One when you applied for or obtained a product or service from
us is also governed by a separate notice entitled Privacy Policy. If you are such an applicant or
customer, please refer to that notice for additional information about our privacy practices.
By using this website or our mobile apps, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy
Statement.
Information We Collect – and How We Collect It
Our websites and apps are not intended to be used by children. We do not intentionally collect
personal information from children under 13 without permission from their parent or legal
guardians. For more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA),
please refer to the FTC's website at ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html.
When you use our website or our mobile apps, we may collect Personal Information that you
submit to us voluntarily, or Online Activity Data that we collect passively.
Personal Information is information such as your name, mailing address, email address,
telephone number, Social Security number, or other information that identifies you. This
information may be collected when you voluntarily provide it to us through forms on our website
or in our mobile apps. These forms could include survey forms, credit card applications, contest
entries, and sign in pages for online banking or mobile application access.
Online Activity Data includes information such as your IP address, browser type, and
display/screen settings; how you interact with our website and mobile advertisements; mobile
device and advertising IDs; social media preferences and other social media data; and other
data that may be aggregated and that doesn't identify individual consumers/customers. This
data may be collected using cookies and other online tracking devices such as pixel tags and
clear GIFs (also known as web beacons), depending on your browser settings. Cookies are small
text files that a website's server places on your computer and can allow websites that you visit
to track your computer's browsing activities. A web beacon is a small string of software code
that represents a graphic image on a website or email. Credit One may also partner with third
parties to deliver advertisements and monitor activities on our own website and other websites.
These partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile
statistics about website visitors. Additionally, Credit One may collect Online Activity Data when
you use our mobile app or your mobile device browser to access our website, i.e. geolocation
data (if you have enabled location services on your device). Credit One may also collect Online
Activity Data or information such as your likes, interests, feedback, and preferences when you
interact with our official pages on social media websites such as Facebook, or from our social
media partners (but only if you choose to share with them and they, in turn, share that
information with us). Please refer to the policies of those companies to better understand your
rights and obligations with regard to your activity on those websites.

How We Use Information
We may use Personal Information and Online Activity Data we have collected for a variety of
reasons, including:
    •    to enable you to apply for a Credit One credit card
    •    to enable you to use online tools or perform certain online transactions
    •    to service and manage your account, including responding to or updating you on
         inquiries, or to contact you about your accounts or feedback
    •    to offer you special products and services and deliver advertisements to you in the form
         of banner ads, interstitial pages (ads that appear as you sign in or sign out of your online
         accounts) or other promotions
    •    to analyze whether our ads, promotions, and offers are effective
    •    to help us determine whether you might be interested in new products or services, and
         to improve existing products and services
    •    to verify your identity and/or location to allow access to your accounts, and conduct
         online transactions
    •    to manage fraud and data security risk
    •    to personalize and optimize your website browsing and mobile app experiences by
         examining which parts of our website you visit or which aspect of our mobile apps you
         find most useful
    •    to comply with federal, state or local laws; civil, criminal or regulatory investigations; or
         other legal requirements
    •    to share with trusted third parties who are contractually obligated to keep such
         information confidential and to use it only to provide the services we have asked them to
         perform. For a description of how Credit One may share information collected from
         consumers who have applied for or obtained a consumer product or service from us,
         please refer to the Privacy Policy.
Managing Your Online and Mobile Preferences
You are not required to provide Personal Information to browse our websites. If you provide us
with Personal Information to obtain a product or service from us, our Privacy Policy governs how
we share Personal Information with our affiliates and third parties.
As you access our online services, cookies and similar technologies allow us to customize
content and advertisements for our products and services on our websites or mobile apps. In
order to make content and advertising as relevant as possible, we may use information about
your relationship with us (such as types of accounts and transactional information). Using
cookies can give you additional or easier access to certain features on our website (such as
allowing you to sign in easier), and can allow us to provide you with more personalized offers.
Currently, our website does not respond to browser "do not track" signals. You can set your
browser to not accept cookies or to indicate when cookies are sent.
Some mobile devices come with a non-permanent advertising identifier or ID which gives
companies the ability to serve targeted ads to a specific mobile device. In many cases, you can
turn off mobile device ad tracking or you can reset the advertising identifier at any time within

your mobile device privacy settings. You may also choose to turn off location tracking on your
mobile device. By turning off ad tracking or location tracking on your mobile device, you may still
see the same number of ads as before, but they may be less relevant because they will not be
based on your interests.
Behavioral Advertising on Third Party Sites
Certain Credit One partners may use unique cookies to collect Online Activity Data on our
website or mobile apps to advertise on third party websites Credit One products and services
that may be of interest to you. Our partners are subject to their own privacy policies. To explore
options for opting out of behavioral advertising, visit aboutads.info/choices or click on the
AdChoices icon in an ad and follow the instructions. You may also use the Network Advertising
Initiative's (NAI) Opt-Out Tool found at networkadvertising.org/choices, or other tools provided
by the publishing platform. Opting out relies on information in the unique cookies placed on
your web browser by our partners, so if you delete cookies, use a different device, or change
web browsers, you may need to opt out again. Additionally, we may partner with websites like
Google and Yahoo to display ads to you based on search terms you use on those websites.
Please review the privacy policies of those websites for instructions on how to limit these ads.
Please note that you may still receive general online advertising from Credit One even after you
adjust your ad preferences with certain web search engines or opt out of online advertising
through AdChoices or the NAI tool. Such advertising, however, will not be based on Online
Activity Data or search term information.
Email
Our marketing emails include instructions on how to opt out of receiving such emails in the
future.
Updating Your Information
Keeping your account information up-to-date is important. You may review or update certain
account information by signing in to your account online. If you cannot change the incorrect
information online, or you prefer to request changes offline, please use the Contact Us option on
our site, or call 1-877-825-3242 or write to us using the contact information listed on your
account statements, records, or other account materials.
Links
Our websites may include links to third-party websites. These third parties are not subject to this
Privacy Statement or to the Privacy Policy. Please review their privacy notices when visiting
these sites.
Information Security
At Credit One, we are committed to protecting your personal and financial information. If we
collect identifying information from you, we will protect that information with security measures
based on internationally recognized security standards, regulations, and industry-based best
practices.

Changes to this Privacy Statement
Credit One may change its online privacy practices in the future and we may revise this Privacy
Statement to reflect material changes. This Privacy Statement was last revised July 1, 2016,
and is effective as of that date.
Glossary
AdChoices: Allows individuals to opt out of browser-enabled interest-based advertising by
some or all participating companies, using opt-out cookies to store your preferences in your
browser.
Browser: An application used for accessing sites or information on a computer network.
Examples include Internet Explorer, Safari, Chrome, and Firefox.
Business partners: Companies we partner with to jointly market and/or deliver products and
services to you. Business partners include affinity or co-brand business partners. They may not
use this information to independently market to you unless you consent.
Cookies: Small pieces of text that are placed in your browser by the websites you visit and the
advertising companies and content partners for those sites. Cookies do not store personal
information.
Privacy Policy: A Credit One product-specific privacy notice, which we provide to customers at
account opening and annually thereafter pursuant to federal law. It describes our privacy
practices and provides you the right to opt out of certain types of information sharing.
IP address: A unique "Internet Protocol" number assigned to a device connected to the Internet.
Credit One treats IP addresses as non-personal information unless otherwise required by law.
Operating system: Software that controls the operation of a computer and directs the
processing of programs, such as Microsoft Windows or Apple Mac OS.
Pixel tags: Software code placed on a website or in an email that transfers information about a
user's activity from your computer to a server connected to the Internet.
Service providers: Vendors with whom we have a contractual relationship to perform services
on our behalf. Vendors may not use personal information for any purpose other than carrying out
those services.
Session: The time from when a customer is signed in to a website to when the customer signs
out.
Social media site: An online platform that allows users to create a public profile and interact
with other users on the website, such as Facebook or LinkedIn.
Third-party websites: Sites that are not owned or operated by Credit One and are not subject
to our Online Privacy Statement.
Web beacon (can be referred to as a pixel or web bug): Enables two websites to share
information. It consists of a small piece of software code that incorporates a graphic image on a

web page or email. Web beacons can be used for activities like site traffic reporting, unique
visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, and personalization.
